Hi,my name's Chandler. I just moved in next door.
你好，我叫錢德，剛搬到對面
Would you like to battle me in a post-apocalyptic world...
想不想跟我在後末日世界
for control of the galaxy's last remaining energy source?
爭奪銀河系僅存的能源？
Sure,neighbor! Come on in!
好啊，請進
Is Janine around?
吉寧在嗎？
She's at dance class.
她去上舞蹈課
Can I check my room?
我可以看看她的房間嗎？
Don't go through her stuff. She gets really mad.
可以，但是別翻她的東西 她會發飆
Oh,my God!
天哪
It's like a guy never lived in here.
一點男人住過的痕跡都沒有
You gotta be careful. This girl thing is dangerous. It's spreading.
小心，這個女性風格很危險 它已經擴散了
It is?
是嗎？
Is this your pretty pink pillow on the couch?
這個粉紅小抱枕是你的嗎？
Is that your tiny little box that's too small to put anything in?
那個什麼都不能裝的小盒子呢
Okay, this is not good. You are a guy,okay?
沒錯，情況很不妙 你是男人，好嗎？
This is a "guy's" place.
這是個男人的家
Soon,you'll be soaking your fingers in stuff.
你一旦失去自覺 就會開始修指甲
And your head's gonna be under a big, brown, drying, big, drying.. It's not good.
你會上美容院烘頭髮… 事情很嚴重
-You're right. I'll talk to her. -Talk to her. Be a man!
你說得對，我會找她談 找她談，做個男子漢
-I'm a man. -Defend yourself!
我是男子漢 保護你自己
We have to hem the new dust ruffle.
錢德，快點，要縫新的除塵布
Be right there,sweetums.
我馬上過去
Totally different situation.
情況完全不同
The One With Ross' Teeth
本集播出：「黑人牙膏效果」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Hey,guys.
你們好
-How was breakfast with Hillary? -Okay.
跟希拉蕊吃飯吃得怎樣？ 還好
She's still depressed because she broke up with her boyfriend.
她還是有點為了失戀而沮喪
Is this Hillary, your hot assistant chef, Hillary?
就是你的性感二廚希拉蕊嗎？
The one that stares at me when I come in?
沒錯 我每次進去都盯著我的那個？
The one who looked at you once because you got in her way.
是你擋路而看過你一眼的那個
Still, I could tell. She was into me.
我還是看得出來她對我有意思
Why don't you set us up?
你幫我們安排一下嘛
Are you setting Ross up with someone? Does she have a wedding dress?
你要幫羅斯找對象？ 她有婚紗嗎？
Come on,I'm serious.
摩妮卡，我是說真的
Okay, I'll do it, but as long as you promise you won't marry her.
沒問題，只要你保證不娶她
Fine,I.. What if she's the one?
好，我… 如果她是我的真愛呢？
Man,you have a problem.
你真的有毛病
Rachel?
瑞秋
I'm making up flyers to try to get new massage clients.
我在做傳單找新客人
Can I come to Bloomingdale's and use the copier?
我可以去布魯明戴爾影印嗎？
Sure, but they might think it's weird since I don't work there anymore.
可以，但他們會覺得奇怪 因為我已經離職了
Oh,my God! What happened?
天哪，怎麼回事？
I got a job at Ralph Lauren.
我跳槽到羅夫羅蘭了
Well, that's great! Congratulations!
太好了，恭喜你
A year ago.
1年了
You've lasted all year! Good for you.
你撐了1年，很好
You could still use the copier where I actually work.
你還是可以去我現在的公司印
But come by at lunch so my boss doesn't see you.
午休時間來，免得我老闆看到
Kim will freak out. She doesn't like me.
否則金會發飆 她本來就不太喜歡我
-I don't think my boss likes me. -I don't think mine likes me.
怪了，我的上司也不喜歡我 我的也是
Maybe it's a universal thing.
或許這是共通現象？
Maybe because you're all hanging around here at 11:30 on a Wednesday.
又或許現在是上班時間 你們卻在這裡打混
Let's head off to work.
上班去吧
-Thank you. -Sure.
謝謝 不客氣
You will not believe this.
說了你一定不信
I was making copies, and Ralph Lauren came in.
我在影印室影印時 羅夫羅蘭走了進來
Oh,my God. Did you talk to him?
天哪，你有跟他說話嗎？
A little. He seems really nice.
一點點，他人蠻好的
-Good kisser. -What?
吻功超棒 什麼
What?
什麼？
-You kissed him? -Totally.
你親了他？ 沒錯
Phoebe, are you serious?
真的還假的？ 真的
He came in and introduced himself.
我在裡面，他進來自我介紹
The next thing I know, we're making out!
然後我們就親熱了
Phoebe,you do know he's married?
菲比，你知道他已婚吧？ 不知道
Phoebe.
菲比
I'm supposed to ask every guy I make out with if he's married?
難道每次跟男人親熱都要先問
No, yeah, I should.
我是該問
Hey, Joey.
喬伊
Can I talk to you for a second? There's a kid in this picture.
可以跟你談一下嗎？ 照片裡這個小孩
Do you know this kid? Is it a relative?
你認識麼 他是你的親戚嗎？
No. I just thought it was cute.
不是，我只是覺得很可愛
That's what I was afraid of. Okay....
我就怕這樣，好
I really want you to feel at home here,but...
吉寧，我希望你住得愉快 不過...
some of this new stuff, it's too girlie.
你有些東西太女孩子氣了
Like what?
像什麼？
Like this. Pictures of cute babies we don't know.
像這個 不認識的可愛寶寶的圖片
We can't have that.
我們不能掛這種東西
Joey, it's Anne Geddes. She's a famous artist.
那是安吉帝斯，她是名藝術家
I don't know this baby. I don't know if she's a famous artist or not.
我不認識這個寶寶 我不知道她是不是名藝術家
I don't want to be a jerk, but you're changing too much around here.
我不想刁難你 但你做的改變太多了
I'm sorry. I wanted to make the place a little nicer.
對不起 我只是想讓家裡舒服一點
But it's too much stuff.
但是也太多了
You know, you got the candles and the "foofy schmoofer" thing here.
你擺了蠟燭和那個什麼東西
Over here, you got a picture of a watering can.
這裡還有一幅花瀝的畫
I just thought..
我以為…
I'm sure it's a famous watering can.
我相信這個花瀝一定很有名
But come on.
但是拜託啦
And what is with the really hot stick in the bathroom?
浴室那個很燙的棒子是什麼？
It's a curling iron.
那是整發器
Well,that's okay then.
那就沒關係
Okay, my towels, for instance. I come into the bathroom...
像我的浴巾，我走進浴室
and my towel is not on the floor, where I keep it.
我的浴巾卻不在地板上
It's up here on some hook. And it smells different.
而是掛在鉤鉤上 味道也不一樣
-It's clean. -It feels different.
它變乾淨了 摸起來也不一樣
It's dry.
它變干了
All right, I can make my peace with the clean, dry towels.
好吧，我可以接受乾淨的浴巾
Also what is with these chips you bought?
還有這些碎片是怎樣？
It's potpourri. You're supposed to smell it.
不，那是乾燥花，是用來聞的
Well, that's like summer in a bowl.
好像夏天被放在碗裡
Kim,hi.
金，你好
I handed in that marketing report, and I never got to hear what you thought.
我一直不知道 你對我的行銷報告的看法
I didn't read it.
我沒看
The spring line's really gonna be great this year, huh?
今年的春裝一定很棒吧？
對
I hear Ralph Lauren fooled around with someone in the copy room.
聽說羅夫羅蘭在影印室 跟某人親熱
Tell me everything.
從頭說起
Hey,guys.
你們好
What's up?
怎樣啊？
You know....
就是…
Oh,my God.
我的天哪
What happened to your teeth?
你的牙齒怎麼了？
I whitened them.
我漂白了
Really?
是嗎？
What do you think?
你們覺得呢？
I think I shouldn't look directly at them.
我覺得我不該直視它
Come on, seriously.
我是說真的
-They're really, really, really white. -What was wrong with your old...
也白得太誇張了 你的...
human teeth?
人類的牙齒呢？
I did leave the gel on a little longer than it said to.
我的確把漂白膠上得比較久
-How much longer? -A day.
久多久？ 1天
Tonight is your date with Hillary.
你知道今晚要跟希拉蕊約會吧
I know. That's why I did it. Are they really that bad?
知道 所以我才漂白牙齒 真的有那麼糟嗎？
You'll be fine. Hillary's blind, right?
不會，放心好了 希拉蕊是瞎子吧？
She will be after tonight.
過了今晚就是了
Oh,Rach. Do you notice anything..?
瑞秋，你有沒有發現…
Your teeth? Yes, I saw them from outside.
你的牙齒？我在外面就看到了
You guys are never gonna believe this...
說了你們絕對不信
but Phoebe made out with Ralph Lauren.
菲比跟羅夫羅蘭親熱
-What? -Oh,my God!
什麼？ 我的天哪
She ran into him at my office, and they just made out.
她去我的辦公室 然後他們就親熱了
The craziest thing is, now my boss likes me because...
最扯的是我因此贏得老闆歡心
it's the best gossip she's heard all year.
她說這是這一整年最棒的八卦
I am proud of all my friends today.
我今天真以我的朋友們為榮
I can't believe Phoebe made out with Ralph Lauren.
菲比居然跟羅夫羅蘭親熱
I'm so jealous!
真是忌妒死了
Hi,I'm Chandler, your live-in boyfriend.
我是錢德，你活生生的男朋友
Chandler, please. Come on.
拜託，
Look at him.
你自己看
Well,I am no woman, but that is one tasty dish.
我不是女人 不過他還真秀色可餐
Here.
拿去…
Who's the silver fox?
那個銀髮老帥哥是誰？
That is your make-out buddy. Don't you recognize him?
那是你的親熱對像 你不認得嗎？
Oh,wait.
等等…
"Phoebe, I love you. Kiss me, please."
菲比我愛你，吻我
That's not Ralph Lauren. It sounds like him,though.
那才不是羅夫羅蘭 不過聲音有像
-What? -Ralph doesn't look like that guy.
什麼？ 羅夫跟他一點也不像
He's young, and he's got long hair and a beard and a Hacky Sack..
他很年輕，長髮落腮鬍 背個大包包
Oh,my God. That's not Ralph Lauren. That's Kenny the copy guy!
天哪，那不是羅夫羅蘭 那是影印小弟肯尼
What?
什麼？
I told my boss that someone made out with Ralph Lauren.
完了，我還跑去告訴我老闆
If she finds out that I lied to her, she'll hate me even more. Phoebe!
要是她發現我騙她 一定會更討厭我，菲比
Why would the copy guy say he's Ralph Lauren?
那個小弟為什麼自稱羅夫羅蘭
To get you to make out with him!
好騙你跟他親熱啊
This will make them look less white.
也許這件能壓住你的白牙
Nope.
不行
Colors that don't work are...
好，沒有用的顏色有
blue,yellow,green,red,black, white,orange and purple.
藍黃綠紅黑白橘和紫
Do you wanna try this highlighter again?
要不要再塗一次亮彩液？
No,I think it poisoned me a little.
不要，我有點反胃
The date starts in an hour. What am I'm gonna do?
離約會只剩1小時 我該怎麼辦
Maybe if your skin was lighter, your teeth wouldn't look so bright.
要是你的膚色白一點 牙齒就不會那麼顯眼
Oh,great! So all I need to do is get some new skin. Thank you.
太好了，所以我去換膚就行了 謝謝你
If we put just a little bit of makeup on you..
我是說你可以化一點妝
Whoa!
We're not 13 anymore.
我們已經不是13歲了
This is the only thing left that has a shot at working.
只剩這個可行的辦法
Won't she notice I have makeup on?
她不會發現我有化妝嗎？
Half the guys out there have makeup on.
拜託，半數的男人都有化妝
What?
什麼？
Half the people.. I mean.. Just try it and see.
半數的人，你就試試看嘛
I am not putting on makeup.
不要，我死也不化妝
Hello? Ross, could you put up some of these flyers for me?
太好了 羅斯，幫我帖幾張傳單好嗎？
No! Demon! Demon!
魔鬼！魔鬼！
Our drawers will smell nice, and we didn't waste these pantyhose.
這樣抽屜就會香香的 舊褲襪也沒浪費
God forbid we throw out old underwear.
是啊，扔舊內衣會遭天打雷劈
You know what? I'm gonna go over to Joey's.
我要去喬伊那邊
We've got to organize the wrapping paper.
我們還要整理包裝紙抽屜
I've really gotten in touch with my feminine side enough today.
對，但我今天已經夠女性化了
In fact, we're two sachets away from becoming a lesbian couple.
再縫兩個香氛袋 我們就要變成女同志了
This has been a girlie day. You're right. I'm sorry.
今天的確很女孩子氣 你說得對，抱歉
I just feel like I need to be in a "guy" place...
不會，我只是想去男人的家
do kind of a "man" thing.
做男人做的事
You go over to Joey's and...
沒錯，去喬伊家吧
drink some beer and hammer up some dry wall.
去喬伊家喝啤酒槌牆壁
When guys hang out, they don't just drink beer and hammer up dry wall.
男人並非只會喝酒槌牆壁
When girls hang out,we don't have pillow fights in our underwear.
女生也不會穿內衣打枕頭仗
I'm sorry. We do.
對不起，我們會
I don't know why I said that.
我不知道為什麼說不會
Hey,Chandler.
錢德
Come on in. We're knitting potholders.
進來，我們在織隔熱手套
No,thanks,Josephine.
不了，喬瑟芬
Ross,I was wondering if..
羅斯，我想說…
Oh,my God! Where are all the men?
天哪，男人都死哪去了？
-Hi,Kim. -Hi,Rachel.
金 瑞秋
Remember what happened yesterday? Well,it didn't happen.
記得我昨天說的事嗎？ 其實沒那回事
You didn't cancel the fabric order?
你沒有取消台灣的布料訂單？
Okay,two things didn't happen.
好，有兩件事沒那回事
Remember I told you someone made out with Ralph Lauren?
我不是說有人在影印室 跟羅夫羅蘭親熱？
Well,it turns out that's not true.
結果是假的
It's not true? That's interesting.
是假的？那就好玩了
Because I checked. Only one keycard was used to access the copier...
因為我去查過 昨天午休時間...
yesterday during lunch, and that keycard belonged to you.
刷卡進影印室的 只有你一個
You think I made out with him?
不…天哪，你以為我跟他親熱
Listen to me...
聽著
sleeping with Ralph is not gonna get you my job.
要是你以為跟羅夫上床 就能坐上我的位子，你就錯了
I don't want your job. I don't.
我不想坐你的位子，真的
This is a mistake. I didn't make out with him.
這真是天大的誤會 我沒跟他親熱，
Nobody made out with him. I didn't use my keycard yesterday.
沒人跟他親熱 我昨天沒用我的卡
I don't even know how to use my keycard.
我連刷卡都不會
-Hi,Ralph. -Hi,Kim.
羅夫 金
Yeah. Nothing happened.
是啊，沒跟他親熱
You could cut the sexual tension in here with a knife.
剛才的情慾張力一觸即發
After that, what could I do except become a chef?
之後我也只能去當廚師
Soon,I hope to open my own restaurant.
我將來想自己開餐廳
You're a really great listener.
你很善於傾聽
Most guys I go out with, they talk and talk.
我交往過的男人多半講個不停
It's like, "Shut your mouth." You know?
聽到後來真想叫他們閉嘴
I've been talking too much. Why don't we talk about you?
我說太多了，來聊聊你吧
Come on,I want to know.
說嘛，我想知道
Okay. I'm from Long lsland.
好，我是長島人
I came to the city for college.
來紐約唸書
I have a 5-year-old son, and in my spare time...
我有個5歲的兒子 平常...
I like to read spy novels. But let's talk more about you.
喜歡看看諜報小說 再來聊聊你吧
If you sear the stems of the flowers first in a frying pan...
很棒的是如果先把花莖底部 在平底鍋上烤一下
your arrangement will look fresh much longer.
花就能開得更久
Joey, that is such a great tip!
好棒的小秘訣
Monica, I need to talk to the girl with the flowers.
摩妮卡，請你出去一下 我有事找那位插花的女士
Okay, but I'm gonna teach you how to make a bird feeder...
喬伊，你待會過來，我教你
out of a pine cone and some peanut butter.
用松果和花生醬做喂鳥器
I love birds.
我最喜歡鳥了
What is the matter with you?
你是怎麼搞的？
-What? -You're arranging flowers!
什麼？ 你在插花
You got dead flowers!
你放枯掉的花
You've got a picture of a baby dressed like flowers!
你掛扮成一朵花的寶寶照片
This is not Joey!
這不是喬伊
Look,I am still Joey, okay?
我還是喬伊，好嗎
Flowers,they're just nice to look at.
花只不過是很好看
And that happens to be a picture by a famous artist of a famous baby.
那是一個名攝影師照的 寶寶也很有名
You're turning into a woman.
你正在變成女人
No,I'm not.
我沒有
Why would you say that? That's just mean.
你怎麼這麼說？ 好惡劣喔
Now I've upset you? What did I say?
我惹你生氣了？我說了什麼？
It's not what you said. It's the way you said it.
不是你說了什麼，是你的口氣
Oh,my God!
天哪
I'm a woman!
我是女人
So now she thinks that I made out with him to get her job.
現在她覺得我跟他上床 好把她踢下去
-Why didn't you just tell the truth? -I did.
你怎麼不跟她說實話？ 我說了
She doesn't think anyone would confuse Kenny the copy guy with Ralph Lauren.
但是她覺得不會有人蠢到 把影印小弟當成羅夫羅蘭
What if Kenny were the real brains behind the whole company?
如果肯尼才是公司的首腦呢？
What if Kenny hired that Ralph guy to be the pretty front man,huh?
搞不好羅夫羅蘭只是個門面
Did she ever think of that?
她想過嗎？
You were with Kenny today.
你今天跟肯尼約會了吧？
Just for a second.
只有一下下
Phoebe, what am I gonna do?
菲比，我該怎麼辦？
The only thing you can do. Sleep with him.
你只好跟羅夫羅蘭上床了
I'm not gonna sleep with him. I mean, I could, but I wouldn't.
我才不跟羅夫羅蘭上床 我可以，但是我不會
Sleep with Kenny.
跟肯尼上床
-That wouldn't help me. -Oh,yes,it would.
那樣對我也沒好處 好處可大了
I've had a really good time tonight.
今晚真的很開心
I rarely connect with someone this much on the first date.
我很少第一次約會 就這麼心有靈犀
Me neither.
我也是
I've had a really good time too, you know.
我也很開心
Are you gonna eat that bread?
你要吃那塊麵包嗎？
I just like the smell.
我只是喜歡聞
You make me laugh.
你好好笑
Would you like to move to the couch?
要不要去沙發上坐？
Maybe I'll just turn down the lights a little?
我把燈光調暗一點好了
How about all the way?
乾脆關燈如何？
Okay.
好
Wow,cool poster.
好酷的海報
Or should I say, "groovy poster"?
還是要說好搶眼的海報
So...
where were we?
剛才聊到哪裡？
Are those your teeth?
那是你的牙齒嗎？
You can see them,huh?
你看得見是吧？
Yes. They're insanely white.
對，白得很嚇人
I did that for you.
我特地為你漂白的
What's the matter with you?
你有毛病嗎？
What's the matter with me? You've got a black light. It's 1999!
我有毛病？你還裝黑光燈 都1999年了
Oh,good. Kim,hi.
太好了，金
Hi,Rachel. I wanted to ask you,have you seen the new Ralph Lauren sheets?
瑞秋，我一直想問你 你看過新的羅夫羅蘭床單嗎？
What am I thinking? Of course you have.
我在想什麼，你當然看過
Okay,look.
好
I'm sorry that I lied to you before.
很抱歉之前對你說謊
You were right. Ralph and I were an item, but we're not anymore.
你猜得沒錯 羅夫和我交往過 但已經結束了
Oh,really?
是嗎？
Yeah,he dumped me.
對，他甩了我
He said, "Rachel, I can't do this.
他說「瑞秋，我不能這樣」
Even though you're a very,very...
「雖然你真的...
very beautiful woman...
很美很美」
I can't do this. I'm married and I'm sorry."
「我不能這樣」 「我有家室，對不起」
But he said, "And you will never get promoted...
然後不知為何他又說 「你永遠也不會升職」
especially not above Kim, who is an integral cog...
「尤其不可能高過金」 「她是羅夫羅蘭體系」
in the Ralph Lauren machine."
「不可或缺的重要人物」
You expect me to believe..
你以為我會相信…
-Hi,Ralph. -Hi,Kim.
羅夫 金
Oh,my God.
天哪
He gave you the coldest look I've ever seen. It's like he hates you!
他看你的眼神好冷酷 彷彿對你恨之入骨
Then it is true!
所以是真的羅
Of course it's true. And it hurts so bad.
當然是真的，我好難過
Oh,honey,come here.
過來，
Oh,it'll be okay.
你會沒事的
We've all been there.
大家都一樣
You and Ralph?
你和羅夫？
Kenny the copy boy.
影印小弟肯尼
「獻給蓋兒約瑟夫」
-I need to talk to you. -What's the matter? You upset?
我有事要說 怎麼了？你心情不好？
Would you like me to get a pint of ice cream and two spoons?
要不要分一桶冰淇淋？
No,no,no ice cream. Look....
不…不要冰淇淋
We gotta get rid of all this girlie stuff in here.
我很抱歉 我們得把這些女生的東西扔掉
I gotta be a man!
我得當個男人
The living room has to remain a guy place,okay?
客廳必須維持男人的風格
That's the way it has to be.
就是這樣
I'll just put it all in my room.
既然如此，我就拿回我房裡
Good. Great.
好 很好
Thanks for being so understanding.
謝謝你的諒解
I didn't want to make a big deal out of this.
我不想搞得很難看
But you could put the picture of the famous baby in my room.
寶寶的照片可以掛在我房裡
I mean,if you want to.
如果你要的話
Okay.
好
And maybe the watering can there.
花瀝的畫也可以
Sure.
好
And a couple of these little tiny boxes.
還有一兩個小盒子
Joey, do you want me to put it all in your room?
喬伊，要不要都放到你房裡？
Okay.
好吧